Hi, I'm Chris Murray, and I'm going to tell you how to find out about English soccer teams.
English soccer teams all are accessible, by the Internet.
The Internet is a very big source, in keeping up with your favorite English teams, and players.
Each one of these teams, that play in the English Premier League, and other divisions in England, all offer their own website.
These websites are very interactive, and are very helpful, in keeping up with the team, your favorite players, and being able to find their stats online.
Also, another way to keep up with your favorite English teams, about watching television.
You can do this by sitting in your own home, in your living room, on your couch, where you're nice and comfortable, on a nice Saturday or Sunday, and watch live English games.
These games are also recorded and replayed all week long.
Many times, these games are offered at different times during the day, some in the morning, and some late at night, so if you're coming home from work, or if you're coming home from school, you can sit down and watch a game whenever.
Also, another time or another place, where you can find these English teams, are at maybe your local pub, where some of these teams and these owners are English, and they offer these games for free, and that's just how you keep up with your English soccer teams.